<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <AncientCorps.DeactivatedMech_Disable>deactivate Mech</AncientCorps.DeactivatedMech_Disable>
  <AncientCorps.Reason_WorkTypeDisabled>work type disabled</AncientCorps.Reason_WorkTypeDisabled>
  <AncientCorps.Reason_NotMechanitor>not a mechanitor</AncientCorps.Reason_NotMechanitor>
  <AncientCorps.Reason_NoEnoughBandwidth>need bandwidth:{0}</AncientCorps.Reason_NoEnoughBandwidth>
  <AncientCorps.DeactivatedMech_TryHack>Try hacking {0}</AncientCorps.DeactivatedMech_TryHack>
  <AncientCorps.DeactivatedMech_CannotHack>Cannot hacking</AncientCorps.DeactivatedMech_CannotHack>

  <DMSAC_World_Takeover>takeover</DMSAC_World_Takeover>
  <DMSAC_World_Takeover_Desc>According to the latest news, a force belonging to {0} took over {2}, which originally belonged to {1}, and now the base has been renamed {3}</DMSAC_World_Takeover_Desc>
  <DMSAC_Level_Rise>raised Defcon</DMSAC_Level_Rise>
  <DMSAC_Level_Rise_Desc>Due to recent events, the {0} command has raised the defend condition level of its units. Their Defcon level is now</DMSAC_Level_Rise_Desc>
  <DMSAC_Level_Down>lowered Defcon</DMSAC_Level_Down>
  <DMSAC_Level_Down_Desc>Based on recent changes in observed activity, {0} Command has lowered its internal alert level. Their Defcon level is now</DMSAC_Level_Down_Desc>
  
  <DMSAC_Level.0>Level O   {0} retained a minimum number of facility patrols and recalled the medium-sized automatroids in the unit and returned them to their bases for maintenance.</DMSAC_Level.0>
  <DMSAC_Level.1>Level I   {0} deployed all-weather patrols between its ground facilities to shorten the reinforcement intervals for attacked facilities, and deployed medium-sized automatroids in the patrol teams.</DMSAC_Level.1>
  <DMSAC_Level.2>Level II  Based on the current situation, {0} will restart some of its large automatroids and mobilize them at any time, and organize a small number of armored platoons as a task force to reinforce ground facilities.</DMSAC_Level.2>
  <DMSAC_Level.3>Level III Due to the recent tense situation, ultra-heavy automatroids have been put on combat readiness and deployed in various areas to provide reinforcement at any time. {0} will carry out armed expulsion of neighboring illegal military sites in accordance with the Colonial Fleet Convention's alert status regulations.</DMSAC_Level.3>
  <DMSAC_Level.4>Level IV  {0} confirmed that the First Hague Convention was no longer applicable to the current situation and issued a formal declaration of war in accordance with the Third Hague Convention. \n\nIn addition, according to Article 2 of the Second Hague Convention, civilians in non-occupied areas who take up arms against {0} forces will be considered combatants as defined by the laws of war.</DMSAC_Level.4>
  <DMSAC_Level.5>Level V   In accordance with the Colonial Fleet Convention's alert regulations, {0} has determined that conditions have been met to warrant an offensive and the mobilization of a heavy armored brigade to conduct the operation. \n\n{0} will occupy and take over identified hostile-controlled areas in compliance with international humanitarian law and the Rome Statute, and strike back at hostile forces that attack facilities in a proportional manner.</DMSAC_Level.5>

  <DMSAC_HackFailed>Hacking failed</DMSAC_HackFailed>
  <DMSAC_HackFailedDesc>Due to {0}'s mistakes, mech was not getting controlled as expected.</DMSAC_HackFailedDesc>

  <DMSAC_CorpNeutral>Communication</DMSAC_CorpNeutral>
  <DMSAC_CorpNeutralDesc>"Code 5, registered personal identified."\n"This is {0}, IFF codes synchronized, cease fire."\n\nThis ancient automatroid command system recognized {1}'s identity. Out of respect for {1}, it has temporarily halted hostilities to your colonists.</DMSAC_CorpNeutralDesc>

  <DMSAC_CorpAlly>Communication</DMSAC_CorpAlly>
  <DMSAC_CorpAllyDesc>"Code 5, registered personal identified."\n"This is {0}, if you require any resources, please formally submit a military surplus requisition form to the {0} logistics office."\n\nOut of trust in {1}, the ancient automatroid command system turned a blind eye to the colonists' actions but issued a warning as per protocol.</DMSAC_CorpAllyDesc>

  <DMSAC_CorpAllyDown>Communication</DMSAC_CorpAllyDown>
  <DMSAC_CorpAllyDownDesc>"Code 5, registered personal identified."\n"This is {0}, paying tribute to the Slayer of Zalta and thanking you for your contributions to the colonization project."\n\nThis ancient automatroid command system recognized {1}'s identity. Out of respect for {1}, it has authorized the colonists to operate freely in this area.</DMSAC_CorpAllyDownDesc>

  <DMSAC_CorpHostile>Reinforcement</DMSAC_CorpHostile>
  <DMSAC_CorpHostileDesc>An automatroid patrol has discovered colonists intruding into a military facility. After a brief preparation period, they will attempt to expel your colonists.\n\nBased on intercepted communication frequency fluctuations, nearby automatroid patrols in this area may be on their way to reinforcement.</DMSAC_CorpHostileDesc>
 
  <DMSAC_CompanyRaid>Attack: {0}</DMSAC_CompanyRaid>
  <DMSAC_CompanyRaid_Desc>A company of automatroids belonging to {0} has surrounded your colony. They are {1}. These automatroids commanded by relay-commanders will launch attacks on colonies and purposefully disarm illegal forces to discourage attacks on their military facilities.</DMSAC_CompanyRaid_Desc>

  <DMSAC_Company.Label>{1}</DMSAC_Company.Label>
  <DMSAC_Company.Desc>This is a {1} affiliated with {0},</DMSAC_Company.Desc>
  <DMSAC_Company.Target>their targets are likely to be {0} within their combat radius</DMSAC_Company.Target>
  <DMSAC_Company.NoTarget>their targets are unknown</DMSAC_Company.NoTarget>
  
  <DMSAC_World_Declaration>War declared</DMSAC_World_Declaration>
  <DMSAC_World_Declaration_Desc>According to the latest news, {0} broadcast a declaration of war against the local faction {1}, and mentioned that all military operations in areas controlled by {1} will be carried out in compliance with the laws of war. \n\nWe don't yet know what impact this will have.</DMSAC_World_Declaration_Desc>
  <DMSAC_World_WarOver>War ended</DMSAC_World_WarOver>
  <DMSAC_World_WarOver_Desc>After taking over the last base, {0} announced that the military operation against {1} had been successfully completed. As a result of the operation, {1}'s influence on the planet was completely eradicated. \n\nAccording to intelligence, this army has returned to its original patrol mode after completing its mission. \nThe war is over...\n\nFor now.</DMSAC_World_WarOver_Desc>

</LanguageData>
